我们给你提供了一个asset drop，看下边的链接，
We're providing you with an asset drop, view the link below,
这样你就可以下载图片然后让他存到你的应用程序里。
so that you can download the images and include them in
当我们打开assets ZIP文件时
the app. When we open up the assets ZIP file, we
我们看到相同的图标以不同分辨率的不同尺寸被提供出来。
see that the same icon is provided at different sizes for
在drawable MDPI文件夹里，我们看到
different resolutions. In the drawable MDPI folder, we see the assets
将要被用到一个MDPI设备里的assets.在drawableHDPI文件夹里
that will be used on an MDPI device. In the drawable
我们看到了将要被用到一个HDPI设备的assets.
HDPI folder, we see the assets that will be used on
这同样适用于其他文件夹。
an HDPI device. And the same goes for the other folders.
在res目录复制所有下载的用于提供的assets的时候，
Under the res directory copy over all the asset
点击一张图片展现他的预览
folders provided in the download. Clicking on an image shows
同时尺寸和像素也被展现出来。
a preview of it and the size and pixels
在这时，你也可以删除老的
is also shown. At this time you can also remove
占位符ic启动图标。我们的新启动图标
the old placeholder ic launcher icons. Our new launcher
就位于mipmap文件夹里。这些是来自drawable文件夹的不同文件夹。
icons are located in mipmap folders. These are distinct folders
如果你建了一个有着
from the drawable folders. If you build an APK
像HDPI那样的目标屏幕分辨率的APK，Android asset
for a target screen resolution like HDPI, the Android asset
packaging工具，AAPT，就可以删除drawable里其他你不需要的决议。
packaging tool, AAPT, can strip out the drawables for other resolutions
但是如果他是在mipmap文件夹里，
that you don't need. But if it's in the mipmap folders,
那么这些assets将被留在APK里不管目标分辨率。
then these assets will stay in the APK regardless of the
但是当你需要一
target resolution. But when would you need an image at a
个分辨率不同于设备的分辨率的图片怎么办？好的，有一个例子就是
resolution different than the resolution of the device? Well, one example
Android launcher应用程序，他控制着主屏幕以及
is the Android launcher app, which controls the home screen as
整个应用程序商店。在设备的当前密度中
well as the All App store. The launcher app won't use
启动应用程序将不用图标，而是
the icon at the current density of the device, but rather
在接下来的最高分辨率中取出一个的图标。对于XXHDP设备就像Nexus 5一样，
pulls a icon for the next highest resolution up. For an XXHDPI device like the
通常情况下assets将从drawable XXHDPI文件夹里
Nexus 5, normally the assets will be pulled
提取出来。但是，在这种情况下，
from the drawable XXHDPI folder. However, in this
启动图标将取出一个XXXHDPI版本启动器图标
case the launcher icon will pull the XXXHDPI
这样就将
version of the launcher icon. That will make
更大的应用程序图标更清晰的出现在
the larger app icons appear sharper on the
所有应用程序屏幕上。因为图标有了新的位置
all apps screen. In the code replace @drawable/ic_launcher
所以我们要在代码中替换掉@drawable/ic_launcher还有@mipmap/ic_launcher。
with @mipmap/ic_launcher because of the new location of the icons.
剩下的图标就是修改预测列表和细节屏幕，
For the rest of the icons modify the forecast list
让他显示正确的天气图标
and the details screen to display the right weather icon
,而不是占位符。看看在老师的笔记中的提示
instead of the placeholder one. See the hints below in
在下边的要点中使用我们的辅助函数，
the instructor notes. Using the helper functions we've provided in
你就可以将天气条件代码映射到你需要的图标上
the gist below, you can map the weather condition code
这就是当你完成
to the icon that you'll need. This is what the
这一步时应用程序应该出现的样子。
app should look like when you're done with this step.
注意每个天气的图标都是有两种类型的，
Note that there are two types of each weather
一个灰色的图标和一个彩色的艺术形象.
icon, a gray icon and a colored art image.
在主要预报中我们将用灰色图标列表。
In the main forecast list we'll be using the
但是，对于今天的布局，我们将用彩色图标。
gray icon. However, for the today layout, we'll use the
当你进到细节活动时，
colored icon. When you go inside the detail activity,
你也将使用彩色图标。在这时，
you'll also use the colored icon. At this time,
你也可以删除任何图片你硬编码到
you can also remove any images you hard coded
XML布局，因为他们现在将被动态填充。
into the layout XML, because they'll be populated dynamically now.